[{"answer": "Tell the truth.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 12, "question": "What's the one piece of advice you would give any president when they walk in the Oval Office for the first time?", "qSentId": 11}, {"answer": "Well, to promote two things.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "What was the overriding concept for the center?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Well, it's a different kind of thing.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Do you feel that you've achieved more outside of the presidency than you did when you were there?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Well, they were.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Just on those two things alone, pretty big ticks in the box, weren't they?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Well, both.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "Did part of you celebrate and the other part slightly think, OK, what's going to happen now?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "I think to promote democracy and freedom.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "Well, what should America's role be?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "I think it was a serious mistake.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "Was that a mistake, do you think?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "Do you think naturally that you are?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Would that be a fair comment?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "I don't -- I'm not sure.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Do you think he means it?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "I don't have much chance to talk to Israeli leaders anymore, but last time I was over there, I did meet with the speaker of the House and I met with the deputy prime minister and also the mayor of Jerusalem.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "To the Israelis who say that you don't fully, I guess, feel their pain of being on the receiving end of the suicide bombing and the attacks and so on, what do you say to them?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Menachem Begin, when he was first elected, had a terrible reputation against peace, against any accommodation, absolutely rigid in his policies.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Are they the people that you could have done business with as president?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Well, I certainly think so.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Could that have happened in Iraq if it had been left to its own devices?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "Well, they are different, but there are basic principles that should be followed.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "Is there a consistent policy that America should pursue with the three or are they all very different cases?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "I think Assad is likely -- very likely to go in the next few months, maybe during this current year.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Should Assad go, though, do you think?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "I don't think America has that kind of confidence.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "And the big question then is how does America respond if it has absolute concrete evidence that Iran now has a nuclear weapon?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "Yes, I did.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "I mean you deliberately avoided any kind of military conflict with Iran when you were president?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "ARTER: I do, because every one of the hostages came home safe and free.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "You still think it would have been a terrible error to do that?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "I think a real threat against Israel, for instance, of an atomic attack, and I'm not sure that the Iranians are going toward a nuclear capability.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "What would need to precipitate that?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "It is absolutely the way it was when I was president.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "This is an exact replica of your Oval Office, isn't it?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "Same furniture, same carpet.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "Same furniture?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "It makes me feel at home.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "When you come in here, how does it make you feel?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Every week.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "And Jimmy and I used to put a table between those two chairs and meet, was it every Wednesday?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "I mean, you were right then and you would be right to say that today, wouldn't you?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "So, you know, the grassroots were there, which you picked up on, but nobody listened?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "I still grow peanuts, I still eat peanuts.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "One of the questions people wanted the answers, do you actually like peanuts?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "I hope everybody will join me in eating peanuts.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "You like peanuts?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Well, I think that entrepreneurial spirit was very important for me as a remote -- as a farm boy on a remote farm, who didn't know anything about the outside world, but was raised with hard work and had a nurturing parents.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Well, he hasn't been able to accomplish very much, because he's been hamstringed by the most uncooperative Congress we've had in history, in my opinion.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "How do you think he's doing as president?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "We don't have any relationship much.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "How do you personally get on with President Obama?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "I wish it was a closer relationship.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "Are you sad about that?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "Well, I was, a bit.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "I heard that you felt a little bit let down when the first chance he got to have you speak at a Democratic Convention, he asked you to do a documentary film instead along with President Clinton, and it was can cut from 20 minutes to four minutes, and that you were a bit cheesed off with this?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "For him to get elected, yes.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Were they good reasons?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "I think he's mistaken.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "When you hear Rick Santorum using you as some stick to batter President Obama, what do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not dangerous to him.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Is he meddling with the wrong guy here?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "That's the indication now.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Has Mitt Romney, from what you're looking at -- has he got it in the bag, do you think?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "I feel that they're going to extremes just to try to get votes.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "When you see that kind of thing, as a very religious man yourself -- a lot of them say, look, we're very religious people; it's all in the Bible -- what do you feel?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "And you think he's doing it deliberately?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "Not quite.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "It's the same thing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "ARTER: Well, he's not a racist, I think.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "What's the difference?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Well, as we mentioned on the program earlier, I think luck has a lot to do with it.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "What are the warning signs for Barack Obama that you would -- if you had the chance, you would say to him, watch this, be careful about that?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "There's another story about him forgetting my Christmas present.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "So he's never moaned again about your timekeeping?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "Well, I think maybe the hardest time we had was when he was when we came home from the White House, because it was the first time we had both been home together all day, everyday.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Sixty five year marriage -- what do you think the secret has been to the longevity of your marriage?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Like I want to go in my office and work without interruption.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "He's the boss.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Who is the boss here?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Ultimately, Rosalynn is.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "We had one time like that.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Or have you just been very lucky that you've never had a period in your life?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Absolutely true.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "ORGAN: So actually writing a book together nearly killed your marriage?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "We gave up our advance on the book back to our publisher.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "What did you resolve from this?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "And you have never written a book again together?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "It's located in very isolated villages that don't have any source of water except a pond that ponds up during the rainy season.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Why Guinea worms?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "43.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "How old is she now?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "It's hard to go to sleep the first night, it was so excited.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "And whether there was a big difference?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "I think there's probably an age limit.", "docId": "120118pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Are you allowed to come back?", "qSentId": 593}]